<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://nexolist.com/sitemap.xsl"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9 http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9/sitemap.xsd" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1">
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/</loc>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/10-celebrities-who-shot-to-fame-through-shear-luck/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-28T08:28:52+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/20/celebrities-who-shot-to-fame-through-shear-luck-02.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[10 Celebrities Who Shot to Fame Through Shear Luck]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/20/celebrities-who-shot-to-fame-through-shear-luck-01.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Today we all know Gibson as a racist, anti-semitic douchebag, but if not for his sister only a few people would be aware of this. See, back in the 1970s when he was working at an orange juice bottling company, his sister Sheila filled out an application without his knowledge to enter the National Institute of Dramatic Art in Sydney. He was accepted and, for better or worse, the rest is history.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/20/celebrities-who-shot-to-fame-through-shear-luck-02.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[If not for the fact of accidentally clicking on the wrong YouTube video, Bieber might be living in relative anonymity in Ontario, Canada. Searching for a different singer, producer Scooter Braun stumbled upon a video that featured Bieber singing at a local singing competition. Impressed, Braun tracked down the theater, school, and eventually Bieber’s mom.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/20/celebrities-who-shot-to-fame-through-shear-luck-031.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[At the age of 4, Gellar was discovered by a talent agent while eating at a restaurant in Upper Manhattan. She was subsequently cast in a Burger King commercial in which she criticized rival McDonalds and declared that she only ate at Burger King. McDonalds actually responded by banning her from eating at their restaurant, which is seriously one of the worst punishments for a kid, especially when you can’t go to your friends’ birthday parties there!]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/20/celebrities-who-shot-to-fame-through-shear-luck-04.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Depp’s original plan was to make it big as a rock star. With his band The Kids, they went to LA to pursue a record deal. However, Lori Anne Allison, the future Captain Jack Sparrow’s first wife, introduced him to Nicolas Cage (!!!), who convinced Depp to get into acting instead and here we are.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/20/celebrities-who-shot-to-fame-through-shear-luck-05.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Pompeo was working as a barmaid in Miami where she caught the eye of fashion photographer Andrew Rosenthal. They began dating and moved to New York City where Pompeo was approached by a casting director who got her some roles in a few commercials before her career really took off.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/20/celebrities-who-shot-to-fame-through-shear-luck-06.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[While on vacation in New York City with her parents, Lawrence was spotted on the streets by a talent scout who took her number and convinced her to try acting. While casting directors were extremely impressed, her mom wasn’t as thrilled. She’s done pretty well for herself though, having been the highest paid actress in the world in 2015 and 2016 and winning an Oscar for Best Actress in 2012 for her lead role in Silver Linings Playbook.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/20/celebrities-who-shot-to-fame-through-shear-luck-07.png</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[As a teenager, Theron worked as a model, but dreamed of becoming a dancer. She attended the prestigious Joffrey Ballet School in New York, but had to give it up when a serious knee injury prevented her from continuing. After making her way to Los Angeles to try acting, she got into an argument with a bank teller who refused to cash a check that her mom had sent to help her pay the rent. A talent agent who happened to standing in line behind her was so impressed with her emotional outburst that he introduced her to casting agents and got her into an acting school.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/20/celebrities-who-shot-to-fame-through-shear-luck-08.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Before getting into acting, Tatum was a college dropout who worked odd jobs as a roofer, an assistant at a vet clinic and even a stripper. He was spotted on a street in Miami by a scout and become a model for Abercrombie and Fitch as well as Armani. But before he made it onto the big screen, his first casting job was as a dancer in Ricky Martin’s 2000 video She Bangs. If you are too young to remember those days, be grateful!]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/20/celebrities-who-shot-to-fame-through-shear-luck-09.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[As a child, Bledel’s mom convinced her to try community theater in order to overcome her shyness. While performing at a shopping mall, a talent scout offered her a contract as a fashion model. From there, her unexpected career really took off.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/20/celebrities-who-shot-to-fame-through-shear-luck-010.png</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[While attending a Canadian Football game, Anderson was spotted on the stadium Jumbotron wearing a Labatt’s Beer T-shirt. The brewing company promptly hired her to be its spokesmodel for a brief period of time before appearing as the covergirl on the October 1989 issue of Playboy. From there, she became the star that we all know today.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/10-european-destinations-worth-visiting-in-2019/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-28T08:28:29+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/16/little-known-european-destinations-worth-visiting-010.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[10 European Destinations Worth Visiting in 2019]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/16/little-known-european-destinations-worth-visiting-01.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[A city that nobody can pronounce. A country that nobody can find on a map (and often gets confused with Slovakia). With a population of around 280,000, one of the smallest capitals in all of Europe, but on a nice day it is perfect for exploring. The city dates back nearly 1,000 years and while the area outside of the city center is fairy drab and “Communist”-looking the center itself is well preserved with a mixture of Romanesque, Gothic, Renaissance and Baroque styles of architecture. While walking around, you have seven bridges to choose from, each with its own unique appearance.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/16/little-known-european-destinations-worth-visiting-02.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[A quarter of a century ago, Sarajevo was a war-torn city full of rubble and despair. But today, it’s a thriving capital that looks part Western Europe and part Istanbul. Its idyllic setting – located in the narrow valley of the Miljacka River at the foot of Mount Trebevic – and religious diversity make it a destination worth visiting. My favorite area was Baščaršija, a bustling market in the historical center of the city that dates back to the 1400s.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/16/little-known-european-destinations-worth-visiting-03.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Named the European Capital of Culture in 2013, Kosice features a massive gothic church known as St. Elisabeth Cathedral as well as a smaller 14th century church called St. Michael Chapel. The city center is lined with open air cafes on either side of the street and you’ll find some really good (and cheap!) locally brewed beer if that’s your thing.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/16/little-known-european-destinations-worth-visiting-04.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Located on the Baltic Sea at the mouth of the River Daugava, Riga is notable for its wooden buildings, art nouveau architecture (with more than 800 buildings in this style) and medieval Old Town. Most of the city center was destroyed during WWII and wasn’t rebuilt until the 1990s, but these days it’s a pretty happening place to be with tons of cafes and nightclubs. Discount airlines such as WizzAir and RyanAir offer really cheap flights to the city.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/16/little-known-european-destinations-worth-visiting-05.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[When people visit Poland, they typically choose Warsaw, Krakow and Wroclaw. But Gdansk is truly an underrated city. This port city along the Baltic Sea has a rich history, having changed hands numerous times during its more than 1,000 years of existence. While the city was almost entirely destroyed during WWII, it was meticulously rebuilt, which surprise a lot of people who are likely to assume that the buildings all date back centuries.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/16/little-known-european-destinations-worth-visiting-06.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Another city located in the Baltics, I loved my visit there because of the varying architecture, the craft beers, and of course the “Republic” of Užupis, a hipster’s paradise that features a statue of Frank Zappa. The old city center really plays up the whole Medieval theme, with girls dressed up as faire wenches (or whatever you want to call them) and hocking souvenirs.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/16/little-known-european-destinations-worth-visiting-07.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Lviv is the most “European” city in all of Ukraine. Rynok Square in the old city center is always bustling and you’ll find cuisine of every variety and tons of in-house beer at ridiculously low prices. If you’re looking to escape from the crowds, Stryyskiy Park is a huge place where you can find a spot to relax undisturbed.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/16/little-known-european-destinations-worth-visiting-08.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[The capital of Croatia, this charming city with cobblestone streets and outdoor cafes is teaming with parks, museums and shops. I had gone there after a couple of days in the beautiful, relatively close Austrian city of Graz, and while it would be an exaggeration to say the two cities are at the same level, I did not find much of a drop-off in terms of living standards once I got to Zagreb.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/16/little-known-european-destinations-worth-visiting-09.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Of the three Baltic capitals (along with Vilnius and Riga), Tallinn was hands down my favorite. The prices are cheap, the atmosphere is unmatched, and at the same time the breeze kept the temperatures comfortable during my August visit. The medieval old city contains narrow, windy streets that make it fun to explore. I had dinner at Olde Hansa, a 15th century restaurant where I drank mead and ate some huge pork thingy where you hold the bone like a handle, probably the way King Henry VIII would have eaten it or something.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/16/little-known-european-destinations-worth-visiting-010.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[At first glance it might seem weird that any city in Belarus would make this list. After all, there is no country in the world – not even Russia itself – that feels more Stalinist than this small former-Soviet country. But Brest is really unexpectedly nice. It feels welcoming and you’ll find all of the coffee shops, parks, and pedestrian streets that make all of those other European cities so appealing. Plus Belarus as a country rarely sees foreign tourists, so it would be something of a novelty both to you and the locals who stumble across you.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/10-models-who-served-as-prototypes-for-the-disney-princesses/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-28T08:31:12+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-011.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[10 Models Who Served as Prototypes for the Disney Princesses]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/gallery/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-010-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Initially, Marilyn Monroe was supposed to model as Tinkerbell, but the studio execs chose Margaret Kerry instead. She gained fame after portraying the fairy in the 1953 Peter Pan cartoon, and even to this day, 89-year-old Margaret receives letters from her fans.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/gallery/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-09-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Initially, Marilyn Monroe was supposed to model as Tinkerbell, but the studio execs chose Margaret Kerry instead. She gained fame after portraying the fairy in the 1953 Peter Pan cartoon, and even to this day, 89-year-old Margaret receives letters from her fans.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-017.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-018.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[One of the newest princesses was the golden-haired Rapunzel. Turns out Taylor Swift agreed to serve as a live model for this heroine! Who would ever say no to such a fantastic offer? Later a legendary photographer Annie Leibovitz even shot her as Rapunzel for Disney parks campaign.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-03.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[After the absolute success of “Snow White” and “Pinocchio”, Disney double-downed on the female-led full-featured animated movies. Instead of sketching out the models, like before, the artists were given movie tapes where they outlined the needed moves, poses, etc., to make them more realistic.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-04.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[After the absolute success of “Snow White” and “Pinocchio”, Disney double-downed on the female-led full-featured animated movies. Instead of sketching out the models, like before, the artists were given movie tapes where they outlined the needed moves, poses, etc., to make them more realistic.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/gallery/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-07-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Let’s face it, Belle is pretty much copy-pasted Judy Garland! The animators really did a great job with her in “Beauty and the Beast”.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/gallery/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-08-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Let’s face it, Belle is pretty much copy-pasted Judy Garland! The animators really did a great job with her in “Beauty and the Beast”.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-013.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[According to animator Mark Henn, he saw an incredibly beautiful young girl with long blueish-black hair in Disneyland and decided she’d make a perfect Jasmine. But there was also a second model – a young actress who goes by the name of Jennifer Connelly.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-014.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[According to animator Mark Henn, he saw an incredibly beautiful young girl with long blueish-black hair in Disneyland and decided she’d make a perfect Jasmine. But there was also a second model – a young actress who goes by the name of Jennifer Connelly.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/gallery/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-016-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Believe it or not, the character and the events Pocahontas goes through are based on the actual Native American Princess Matoaca also known as “Pocahontas”. But her appearance was inspired by that of Hollywood Native American actress Irene Bedard.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/gallery/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-015-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Believe it or not, the character and the events Pocahontas goes through are based on the actual Native American Princess Matoaca also known as “Pocahontas”. But her appearance was inspired by that of Hollywood Native American actress Irene Bedard.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-01.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Rotoscoping is nothing new today, but back in the day, it was a phenomenal breakthrough in animation. “Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs” was created with the help of this technique. A dancer Marge Champion was chosen from more than two hundred contenders to become the real-life Snow White, and she nailed it.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-02.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Rotoscoping is nothing new today, but back in the day, it was a phenomenal breakthrough in animation. “Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs” was created with the help of this technique. A dancer Marge Champion was chosen from more than two hundred contenders to become the real-life Snow White, and she nailed it.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-011.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[When creating the Little Mermaid, the artists didn’t know if they really needed a model. After all, by the time this movie came out, rotoscoping had not been used in the studio for 30 years. But of course, in the end, they did use the 16-year-old Alyssa Milano.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-012.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[When creating the Little Mermaid, the artists didn’t know if they really needed a model. After all, by the time this movie came out, rotoscoping had not been used in the studio for 30 years. But of course, in the end, they did use the 16-year-old Alyssa Milano.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/gallery/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-05-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[In case you didn’t know Audrey Hepburn was a real life sleeping beauty Aurora.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/gallery/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-06-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[In case you didn’t know Audrey Hepburn was a real life sleeping beauty Aurora.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/9/10-realnyh-krasavitc-stavshih-prototipami-disneevskih-printces-019.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[As you may know, Princess Tiana, the main character of “The Princess and the Frog” was the first black girl among the Disney princesses.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/10-richest-rock-stars-of-all-time/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-28T08:25:46+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/23/richest-rock-stars-081.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[10 Richest Rock Stars of All Time]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/23/richest-rock-stars-01.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[That’s a decent amount of dollars, isn’t it? Johnny Cash made music successfully for pretty much his entire life, so it’s only natural he saved himself a nice paycheck.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/23/richest-rock-stars-02.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Dave isn’t the most known person outside of the US, but he’s won two Grammys already. He’s still relatively young – only slightly over 50 – so he could go on for a few more years, maybe even adding some money to his net worth.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/23/richest-rock-stars-031.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Considering how much Keith has probably spent on drugs, that’s a healthy financial situation he’s in.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/23/richest-rock-stars-04.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[He wrote Yellow Submarine and lots of other Beatles songs and made plenty of money from his part in the most successful band in history.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/23/richest-rock-stars-051.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Well, Mick Jagger is awesome. What else can I say?]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/23/richest-rock-stars-06.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[He should probably repave that yellow brick road with golden bricks at this point.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/23/richest-rock-stars-071.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[While Jimmy might not have earned most of this money on his music – since it’s hard to argue he’s “bigger” than Elton John or the Rolling Stones – his business ventures don’t take away the fact that he is in fact a rock star. He’s made loads of music and has had a hand in record labels, beer, real estate, a casino and football team the Miami Dolphins.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/23/richest-rock-stars-081.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[One of the best singers of the 80s, U2’s Bono has turned into a PR man for charity (especially – ironically – ones dealing with poverty) in recent years.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/23/richest-rock-stars-09.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Imagine all the people living life in peace? More like imagine $800 million on your bank account!]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/23/richest-rock-stars-10.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Paul is still making music until this day (he actually recently released a new album) and holds most of the copyrights for the Beatles music, so him being on top of this list only makes sense. But damn, that’s a lot of money.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/10-winters-sports-that-should-be-in-olympic-games/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-28T08:30:56+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/10/winters-sports-08.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Ice climbing]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/10/winters-sports-01.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Picture water-based kiteboarding. Now imagine wearing skis or snowboarding footwear and being able to travel uphill or downhill with the help of the wind. That’s what snowkiting is all about. The sport began to develop in the 1980s, but it wasn’t until the 2000s that it really began to gain attention. If this description has suddenly inspired you to give this sport a try, be aware that it’s the most dangerous activity on our list. In particular, if you’re riding on sleep slopes blocked winds and turbulence can cause the kite to behave erratically and even send you crashing to the ground far below.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/10/winters-sports-02.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Ever dream of asking your dog, “Who’s a good Olympic gold medalist, huh? Who’s a good Olympic gold medalist? Yes, you are!” Dog sled racing is one of the paths that can turn this dream into a reality. In fact, this sport has found its way into the Winter Olympics as a demonstration sport on three occasions (most recently during the 1994 games in Lillehammer, Norway), but there don’t seem to be very many people who are hankering for it to receive official event status.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/10/winters-sports-03.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Whether you’re a professional racer or a casual enthusiast, karting is a hell of a lot of fun. What could possible beat zooming your way through a quarter-mile track against your friends in a tiny little machine? Well, how about doing it on a frozen lake? Ice karting involves all of fun of regular karting, but with more slipping and sliding. If any sport deserves Olympic consideration, this should be the one.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/10/winters-sports-04.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Take something like a volleyball or soccer ball. Grab some brooms. Attempt to whack the ball into the goal net. This is basically the kind of game that your PE teacher would throw together. While it is played on a hockey rink, it doesn’t involve ice skates and therefore doesn’t require you to know how to skate. There is some controversy over who actually invented the game. Canada says they did. Sweden takes exception to that claim. The only way to really settle this argument is through a game of broomball, we suppose.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/10/winters-sports-05.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Snow kayaking is exactly like water kayaking, but – get this – it’s on snow instead!!! Hope that wasn’t too difficult to explain. There isn’t a hell of a lot more to say about this sport other than the fact that it sounds like a stunt that they would have done on MTV’s Jackass way back when.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/10/winters-sports-06.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Creating a ski ballet was pure, unadulterated lunacy. It featured skiers doing these choreographed 2-minute routines down slopes while flipping, prancing and doing pirouettes to music. Ski ballet actually did make it as far as a demonstration sport at the 1988 games in Seoul, but the results were so disastrous that by 2000 the International Ski Federation had discontinued all formal competitions under its flag altogether.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/10/winters-sports-07.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[At first, I assumed this was like water polo but with athletes diving around in snow, and that thought got me excited! But no, it’s actually the horse kind of polo. But colder and snowier. Consequently, St. Moritz, Switzerland has been hosting the pre-eminent snow polo tournament since 1985, so it has something of a following.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/10/winters-sports-08.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Ice climbing became an officially sanctioned sport in 2002, making it a relatively new sport. Unlike the other sports on this list, ice climbing would actually make perfect sense as an Olympic event. It’s basically like attempting a 100 meter sprint, but doing it vertically. It requires strength, precision, and nerves of steel. Of course, it would also be kind of cool if they had to allude somebody whose job it was to yank them off the ice American Gladiators-style.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/10/winters-sports-09.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[This is another sport that is fairly self-explanatory. You grab some skis, latch yourself to the back of a truck, horse or a pair of dogs, and do all sorts of ski-related things like navigating around slalom gates, doing jumps, and all that good stuff. It sounds like an idea that somebody would come up with while drunk, basically.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/10/winters-sports-010.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[If you were hoping this sport involved actual polar bears taking part in swimming events, sorry to burst your bubble. We’re talking about Olympic athletes swimming across icy lakes. It’s all about doing the polar bear plunge, but getting rewarded with a medal for being faster than the rest of the insane competitors.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/11-delicious-street-foods-from-all-over-the-world/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-28T08:29:48+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/14/11-Popular-Street-Foods-From-All-Over-the-World-09.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[11 Delicious Street Foods From All Over the World]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/14/11-Popular-Street-Foods-From-All-Over-the-World-11.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Although it is thought to have originated in Egypt and is popular all over the Middle East, Israel is where this deep-fried ball made from ground chickpeas, fava beans or both. It is often served on a pita with hummus, yogurt or tahini sauce.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/14/11-Popular-Street-Foods-From-All-Over-the-World-02.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[The invention of the currywurst is attributed to Herta Heuwer, who in 1949 opened a food stand to feed hungry construction workers who were rebuilding a devastated Berlin, this German dish consists of a pork sausage that is first steamed and then fried, cut into slices, and topped with curry ketchup. It’s usually served with French fries or a bread roll. While you’ll find it all over Germany, Berlin and Hamburg are the two cities where this is especially popular.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/14/11-Popular-Street-Foods-From-All-Over-the-World-03.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Gimbap is basically South Korean sushi, with the main difference being that the rice in the Japanese version is mixed with rice vinegar, sugar and salt while Gimbar is seasoned with salt and sesame oil. The rice and ingredients such as shrimp, spicy tuna, kimchi and squid are rolled in gim, which are dried sheets of nori seaweed, and served in bite-sized slices.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/14/11-Popular-Street-Foods-From-All-Over-the-World-04.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[The nice thing about these puff pastries – typically made by elderly ladies with a real knack for baking – is the different types of fillings that they can be made with. You can get them with beef, potato, cabbage, cheese, and even buckwheat.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/14/11-Popular-Street-Foods-From-All-Over-the-World-05.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[You can’t visit Hong Kong without trying one of these spherical egg-based waffles. Made of eggy leavened batter, they are generally served hot and eaten plain, although they can also be served with coconut, fruits such as strawberry, and chocolate sauce.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/14/11-Popular-Street-Foods-From-All-Over-the-World-06.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[These thin pancakes are beloved enough that France celebrates National Crepes Day on February 2nd. You can eat them for breakfast or as dessert. In addition, if you’re in the mood for something sweet, you can get yourself some crepes filled with strawberries and cream or Nutella. On the other hand, if you’re looking for a savory snack, you can order them with such fillings as chicken, cheese, mushrooms, ratatouille or eggs.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/14/11-Popular-Street-Foods-From-All-Over-the-World-07.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Banh Mi is a popular Vietnamese sandwich comprised of a baguette that is served with things like pork sausage, cucumber, coriander leaf, pickled carrots and daikon. In a nod to Vietnam’s French colonial past, condiments such as pâté and mayonnaise are also added. While typically savory, ice cream can also be used as a filling.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/14/11-Popular-Street-Foods-From-All-Over-the-World-08.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[The baozi is a type of bun filled with meat or vegetables and is usually steamed. There are a variety of dipping options including vinegar, soy sauce, chili or garlic paste, oils, coriander and leeks or sesame oil. Having lived in Beijing for 4 months, I can attest that these can be found by street food vendors all over the city.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/14/11-Popular-Street-Foods-From-All-Over-the-World-09.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Although the Chimney Cake originated in the Hungarian-speaking part of Transylvania (today’s Romania), it has gained huge popularity in Prague, where you can find numerous vendors making this spit cake (known as Trdelník in Czech) in the old city center.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/14/11-Popular-Street-Foods-From-All-Over-the-World-10.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[So technically this isn’t street food. But when visiting Taiwan, you definitely need to get yourself a glass of bubble tea. It consists of a tea of some kind (i.e., oolong, black or green tea), milk in some form (fresh, condensed or powdered) and sugar (optional). But the real appeal is the chewy tapioca balls, popping boba, or fruit jellies that are added to the beverage.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/14/11-Popular-Street-Foods-From-All-Over-the-World-011.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Made of rye or wheat flour, these traditional pastries in the Karelian area of Finland are also enjoyed in nearby Russia and Estonia. The most typical version has a thin rye crust with a filling of rice.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/11-most-anticipated-video-games-of-2019/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-28T08:29:31+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/15/upcoming-games-2019-10.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[11 Most Anticipated Video Games of 2019]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/15/upcoming-games-2019-01.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[The first one was critically acclaimed success and ever since the trailer for the second one dropped, people have been anxious for it. If it’s even half as good as the first one, it’ll blow everyone’s mind.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/15/upcoming-games-2019-02.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[It’s Rockstar – you know this is coming sooner or later. PC players deserve to be cowboys too.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/15/upcoming-games-2019-03.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[An anime/vampire Dark Souls? This looks like an action-packed heap of fun, with – of course – infuriating boss fights.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/15/upcoming-games-2019-04.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[The first one wasn’t all that known, but it was a more than decent game. The second one looks like it’s going to turn it up a notch, so be sure to keep an eye on this one. It’s like a more realistic version of Borderlands!]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/15/upcoming-games-2019-05.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Disney meets Final Fantasy – and we’ve been waiting for the third one for quite a while! Well, technically it’s more like the fifth (or sixth?) one, but you know what I mean.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/15/upcoming-games-2019-06.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[This gorgeous platformer is getting a sequel that’ll be sure to keep us entertained for several hours once more.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/15/upcoming-games-2019-07.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[No one expected this one to come, especially since the first was released back in 2013. If you’re into storytelling and a darker version of classic fairy tales, this one might be for you.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/15/upcoming-games-2019-08.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[It’s the new game by FromSoft, the guys that gave us Dark Souls. Not much is known about it, apart from the fact that it’s sure to cause some controllers being thrown against walls again.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/15/upcoming-games-2019-09.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[And we all thought this series was getting rebooted after DmC, huh? Well, apparently they’re moving on with number five now, and Nero and Dante look ready for action!]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/15/upcoming-games-2019-10.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[An open world cyberpunk first-person RPG from the developers that made The Witcher 3. This can only be good. Very good.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/15/upcoming-games-2019-11.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[The base game was Capcom’s best selling game to date and the expansion is going to add more of the stuff we love: monsters to carve up for weapons and armor!]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/11-weird-celebrities-in-the-entertainment-industry/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-28T08:30:17+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/12/Ten-Strangest-Celebrities-11.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[11 Weird Celebrities in the Entertainment Industry]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/12/Ten-Strangest-Celebrities-01.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Phoenix is one of the most talented actors in Hollywood today, having been nominated for three Oscars and generating a lot of buzz in his new role as the Joker. But he is also notoriously reclusive. He made headlines back in 2009 when he basically mumbled his way through a David Letterman interview while wearing a beard and sunglasses. He continues to act painfully awkward to this day, although in fairness, if you grew up in a communal cult and watched your brother River die of a drug overdose right in front of you, you would probably be something of a tortured soul yourself.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/12/strangest-celebrities-02.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[From the mid 90s through the early 2010s, Nicolas Cage was one of the biggest stars on the planet. In fact, he even accumulated $150 million in wealth…and somehow proceeded to blow through all of it. But it isn’t necessarily his free spending ways that landed him on this list. He just so happened to name his son Kal-El (which was Superman’s name on Krypton), bought a tyrannosaurus rex skull for some reason, and purchased a full-sized pyramid that he intends to be buried in when he dies.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/12/strangest-celebrities-03.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[LaBeouf was once regarded as Hollywood’s biggest up-and-comer, but he seems more famous for getting into trouble. First, there was the Chicago Walgreen’s incident back in 2007 in which he was arrested for criminal trespassing. Likewise, he was arrested in 2014 for refusing to leave the Studio 54 Theater. He’s been known to wear a paper bag on his head at red carpet events. Oh, and when he released his short film Howard Cantour.com, it was immediately discovered that he had completely plagiarized the script from Ghost World creator Daniel Clowes’ comic Justin M. Damiano. As if nobody would notice?]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/12/strangest-celebrities-04.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[The over-the-top fitness guru Simmons is best known for his flamboyant, enthusiastic personality, and of course those sequined tank tops and way-too-short shorts. He also had a $10,000 replica doll of Barbra Streisand made and even sent her a $100,000 ring that he had purchased at Tiffany’s. She sent it back because… they’ve never even met! Today Simmons never leaves his mansion. Rumors have swirled that his housekeeper is holding him captive, although he has denied this.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/12/strangest-celebrities-05.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Few singers are as quirky as Lady Gaga. She’s worn dresses made out of meat, she also dressed up as a giant egg during her appearance at the 2011 Grammys – and even claims she stayed in it for 72 hours. Her weirdness certainly has paid off.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/12/strangest-celebrities-06.png</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Showing up in that infamous swan dress to the 2001 Oscars would have been enough to put her on this list, but almost two decades later she still occasionally makes the news for being a big weirdo. There was that incident at the airport in Thailand when she attacked a reporter who asked a fairly normal question. Then there was that…other incident at an airport (this time in New Zealand) when she tore the shirt off a photographer. Let’s not forget about that rainbow-colored Afro wig and fake beard she wore while on tour in 2013.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/12/strangest-celebrities-07.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Busey’s career got off to a good start when he was nominated for an Oscar for his portrayal of Buddy Holly in the movie The Buddy Holly Story. But he’s had all sorts of problems including overdosing on drugs, getting into a motorcycle accident that caused brain damage, and getting into a fist fight with a reporter who was skeptical of Busey’s claims that he had visited heaven after the aforementioned motorcycle crash. There was also that time when he sprayed two Swedish reporters with a hose and threatened to attack them with a rusty machete, which begs the question: who the hell carries around a rusty machete?]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/12/strangest-celebrities-09.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Depp has always had kind of a reputation for being odd, and not just because he always plays the weirdest character in every Tim Burton movie. Due to terrible money mismanagement he has managed to burn through around $650 million dollars! To do that, you’d have to pretty much buy up all of the planets in the solar system. When it was reported that he spends $30,000/month alone on his wine drinking habit, his retort was that was “far more” than that. There’s the time, according to Penelope Cruz, when they went out for dinner and Depp tried pulling out one of his teeth.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/12/Ten-Strangest-Celebrities-10.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Where to start with Franco? How about the time he asked his assistant to take his girlfriend to the hospital instead of taking her there himself? But at least he feels kind of bad about it now. He once appeared in public with a tattoo of Emma Watson on his neck – which freaked a lot of people out – only to reveal it was a fake. He threw himself a Bar Mitzvah at 37. When he was a struggling actor, he worked at a McDonalds and tested out different accents when serving customers. The list goes on and on, guys.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/12/Ten-Strangest-Celebrities-11.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[How could West not make this list? An entire book could be written about the most eccentric rapper of all time. He once Tweeted an uplifting prayer and “accidentally” included a picture of his wife in her underwear. He showed off pictures of his gigantic mansion that could probably double as a monastery. There was practically nothing inside of it. Let’s not forget Taylor Swift. Meeting Donald Trump in the Oval Office. Repealing the 13th Amendment (which abolished slavery, if you need a reminder). The dude is bananas.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/12-famous-persons-who-made-it/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-28T08:31:32+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/2/1-2.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Ed Sheeran]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/2/1-2.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/2/2-3.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/2/3-3.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/2/4-3.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/2/5-3.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/2/6-3.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/2/7-3.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/2/8-3.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/2/9-3-1024x612.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/2/10-2.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/2/11-3.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/2/12-3.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/6-movies-roles-nobody-wanted/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-12-08T05:16:00+02:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/26/unpopular-movie-parts-04.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Bella Swan – Twilight]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/26/unpopular-movie-parts-01.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Jodie Foster only got this role because Michelle Pfeiffer and Meg Ryan rejected it before her. They both refused for the same reason: they found the movie very disturbing.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/26/unpopular-movie-parts-02.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Before Al Pacino was cast, Jack Nicholson and Martin Sheen were asked. Jack Nicholson declined because – and this is a quote – he believed “Italians should play Italians”.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/26/unpopular-movie-parts-03.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Let’s be honest: no one wants to play the guy that falls in love with a girl only to… stay in love with that girl? I mean, what’s this character’s evolution in the movie anyway. He just keeps loving her. While that might sound romantic, it’s very boring artistically speaking.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/26/unpopular-movie-parts-04.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[This role was turned down by many actresses because of reasons ranging from “I don’t care” to “I think this script is awful”. Both are valid reasons to not be associated with this project in any way, shape or form.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/26/unpopular-movie-parts-05.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Let’s be honest here: would *you* play in that movie? I mean, the book is bad, but it’s an artistic masterpiece compared to the movies.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/26/unpopular-movie-parts-06.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[The first people on Peter Jackson’s list were Nicholas Cage, Daniel Day Lewis and Russell Crowe. They all didn’t want the part for different reasons, which led to Viggo Mortensen getting to play Aragorn.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/7-movies-to-watch-if-you-love-bird-box/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-28T12:47:40+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/24/movies-like-bird-box-07.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[7 Movies to Watch If You Love Bird Box]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/24/movies-like-bird-box-01.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[The Happening probably has most in common with Bird Box in terms of how the “incident” begins. It’s also an event that causes people to commit suicide and some people have to somehow survive in the fallout. It’s worth a watch I guess.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/24/movies-like-bird-box-02.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Where Bird Box is about not looking at something, A Quiet Place is pretty much the same movie but about a family trying to survive in a world where you can’t make any noise.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/24/movies-like-bird-box-03.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[You’ve probably seen this one already, but it’s Tom Cruise trying to survive through an alien invasion. It’s amazing, because it has Tom Cruise in it.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/24/movies-like-bird-box-04.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[If you’re just looking to see Sandra Bullock get through some scary moments, Gravity would also perfectly fit that bill for you.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/24/movies-like-bird-box-05.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Another post-apocalyptic movie where a parent has to navigate his child through a world that’s entirely gone to Hell.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/24/movies-like-bird-box-06.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[This movie has a deaf girl being stalked by someone that manages to get inside her house. That’s scary even if you can hear him coming!]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/24/movies-like-bird-box-07.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[This amazing movie is also mostly a psychological horror movie in the sense that it has no jump scares but you’ll feel uneasy for pretty much the entire length of the movie. Not only that, but you’ll even be thinking about it for days or weeks after watching it!]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/8-biggest-life-changes-in-the-last-20-years/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-28T08:27:18+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/21/how-life-changed-07.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[8 Biggest Life Changes In The Last 20 Years]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/21/how-life-changed-01.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[This is probably the most obvious one. A couple of decades ago, smartphones – actually, regular cellphones as smartphones didn’t exist yet – were only for the rich and were considered a luxury. In our current day and age, most people can’t even imagine living without one.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/21/how-life-changed-02.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[We eat out more, and restaurants pay more attention to presentation. There’s no better marketing plan than your clients posting your food all over Instagram.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/21/how-life-changed-03.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Ever since 9/11, terrorism has become a genuine threat for most countries at most times. We’re still seeing the occasional terrorist attack every now and then, everywhere around the world.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/21/how-life-changed-04.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Classic television has taken a backseat because of streaming services like Netflix. You can now watch your favorite shows on the road, as long as you have a connection to the internet. Which is pretty much everywhere these days.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/21/how-life-changed-05.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Hey – it’s not all bad! No second-hand smoke!]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/21/how-life-changed-06.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[No matter how much we want to deny it – who hasn’t watched their work mails when on holiday? Just a quick peek now and then won’t hurt, right? Wrong!]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/21/how-life-changed-07.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[The president’s Twitter account is one of the best. It’s the greatest in the business, believe me.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/21/how-life-changed-08.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Honestly, voicemail had a pretty short lifespan. If someone doesn’t answer, just text them. Voicemail is entirely useless.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/8-lessons-i-learned-from-strong-woman/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-26T20:18:51+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8/8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship5.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[8 Lessons I Learned From Strong Woman]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8/gallery/8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship8-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8/gallery/8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship7-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8/gallery/8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship6-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8/gallery/8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship5-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8/gallery/8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship4-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8/gallery/8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship3-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8/gallery/8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship2-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8/gallery/8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship1-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8//8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship1.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Being respectful to each other is the corner stone of a successful and happy relationship. A strong woman knows this and will not tolerate offensive language, bad treatment, belittling comments about her looks, hobbies, work, etc. She’s open to healthy criticism, but without sarcasm and negativity. She’s been there, done that, and now wants someone who will make her happy, not miserable.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8//8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship2.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Lying is something a strong woman simply can’t stand. She would rather hear a blunt or harsh truth than stay in the dark not knowing what’s going on. Sugar-coating things is definitely not her style and she wouldn’t want her partner to do it either.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8//8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship3.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Insecurity leads to jealousy and all kinds of weird behaviour in a relationship. A partner that feels insecure will not be able to fully trust her, no matter how perfect she behaves herself. That’s why a strong woman doesn’t tolerate insecurity that results in unkindness, suspiciousness, and low self-esteem. A guy like that will not stay in her life for long even if he somehow finds his way into her heart.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8//8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship4.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[A strong woman is unforgiving when it comes to those who are unfaithful. It’s the worst kind of lie, one she will never let go. If a partner wants to see some other women as well, he should discuss this beforehand, discussing the boundaries of such a relationship. Otherwise, she’ll let go of a partner like that in a heartbeat.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8//8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship5.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[She’s strong and confident, but this doesn’t change the fact that she wants her partner to be all that, too. She knows her weaknesses and had moments of doubts and various hardships, that’s when her partner should support her and be there for her in every way. In other words, she’s looking for a mature man she can fully trust.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8//8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship6.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Inside the relationship we all have certain expectations and when they’re not met we try various tricks to get what we want. Just like women, guys have a rich arsenal of manipulative instruments they’re not afraid to use. Maybe he would like his girlfriend to be more fit, so he’ll try to push her into going to a gym by implying she’s overweight. He may also try to make her wear things he finds attractive, ignoring her opinion on the matter, just to show off what a woman he’s got. Well, all these tricks don’t work on her! And she will not tolerate if a partner tries to overpower her in such a way.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8//8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship7.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[While most ladies have a hard time figuring what they like and what is too much, a strong woman knows exactly where her boundaries lie, especially when it comes to relationships. If says ‘No’ or ‘Don’t you ever do that again’ – she means it and she will not tolerate her partner overstepping her boundaries over and over again.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/8//8-things-a-strong-woman-will-never-tolerate-in-a-relationship8.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Men are quite used to being the lead in the relationship, that’s why being together with a strong woman is tricky. She’s independent, free-spirited, and will hop into the driver’s seat whenever she feels like it or things that she has a better understanding of things. In this case, a partner should let her lead the way! Being too dominating, always trying to decide things for her and not consulting with her on different matters will definitely lead to breakup. A strong woman won’t tolerate such behaviour.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/8-places-that-look-like-a-wonderland-in-the-winter/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-28T08:30:42+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/11/places-in-the-world-that-look-like-a-winter-wonderland-07.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[8 Places that Look Like a Wonderland in the Winter]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/11/places-in-the-world-that-look-like-a-winter-wonderland-01.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[When most people are feeling festive about wintertime, they build a snowman. But Harbin, China takes it to entirely different level. This city of more than 5 million, located in the frigid northern end of the country, hosts an annual ice and snow sculpture festival, an event that attracts talented artists from all over the world who show off their mad ice sculpture skills. We don’t mean a quaint sculpture of a life-size penguin or whatever either. They go all out and create these huge ice castles, towers, trains and basically anything that would make you feel like you’ve entered a fantasy world.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/11/places-in-the-world-that-look-like-a-winter-wonderland-02.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[The village of Grindelwald in the Bernese Oberland is nestled between the mountains of Eiger and Wetterhorn. The breathtaking mountainscape makes for an unforgettable winter holiday experience. Going for walks in the village or renting a car and visiting the quaint surrounding villages are just a few ways to keep yourself occupied. As a bonus, if you’re into snowboarding, this is the perfect place to show off your McTwist maneuver or whatever it’s called.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/11/places-in-the-world-that-look-like-a-winter-wonderland-03.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Part of a UNESCO World Heritage region, Hallstatt is the oldest village in Austria, having been settled around 100 BC. In the winter time you can enjoy the powder snow, dog sledding, and skiing activities. In the evenings you can go on a leisurely walk through the village by torch light. In addition, you can take the Skywalk up the mountain and get a panoramic view of this wintery paradise.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/11/places-in-the-world-that-look-like-a-winter-wonderland-04.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[When it comes to winter wonderlands, it is difficult to think of a place that encompasses this idea more than Lapland. This place located in northern Finland might as well have come from the pages of a children’s fairytale. When you take in the vast amounts of snow, the enchanting buildings and the forests totally covered in white, it almost makes you feel like it was created on a fake Hollywood set. Just wait until evening though. That’s when the Northern Lights appear and create magic in the sky.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/11/places-in-the-world-that-look-like-a-winter-wonderland-05.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[The Blue Ice Caves of Iceland are natural phenomena that are formed in glaciers during winter. The blue color occurs when snow falls on the glacier, is compressed and becomes part of it. Air bubbles form and are squeezed out, which results in enlarged ice crystals that create the blue appearance.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/11/places-in-the-world-that-look-like-a-winter-wonderland-06.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[While this town of around 70,000 is popular all year round because of the mountains and its unspoiled wilderness of fjords, winter is the best time to go because of the Northern Lights. There are also plenty of shops, cafes and restaurants on Storgata, the town’s main pedestrian street. You can also cuddle with the calm and friendly reindeer!]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/11/places-in-the-world-that-look-like-a-winter-wonderland-07.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a winter fairytale destination without the huge crowds of tourists, head over to Moraine Lake on the Canadian side of the Rocky Mountains. During the wintertime, the lake freezes over, making it a perfect place to enjoy a walk. The small also home to an ice sculpture festival.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/11/places-in-the-world-that-look-like-a-winter-wonderland-08.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[When a city names itself North Pole, what would you expect? If you answered, “Tropic island?” then you’re obviously being sarcastic as hell. This small Alaskan village of 2,000 residents just outside of Fairbanks takes the Christmas season extremely seriously. When you walk around, you’ll find street names such as Kris Kringle, Mistletoe and Snowman Lane. Of course, Santa Claus also has a house there, and you can totally visit it!]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/9-best-foods-to-gain-muscle-mass/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-28T08:26:28+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/22/muscle-mass-foods-03.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[9 Best Foods to Gain Muscle Mass]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/22/muscle-mass-foods-011.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Beef has lots of protein and fats that’ll help you gain muscle mass really fast. There’s healthier alternatives, probably, but there’s nothing like a good steak.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/22/muscle-mass-foods-02.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Again: you’re looking for protein and fats. Same rules apply here.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/22/muscle-mass-foods-03.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Tuna – and fat fish in general – has lots of good stuff for your body, including protein. And it’s got no carbs! They also have those sweet omega-3 fatty acids, which can slow the loss of muscle mass.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/22/muscle-mass-foods-04.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[White meat is the best meat when you’re trying to gain muscle mass. Chicken especially has incredible amounts of protein in it, which will easily grow muscle.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/22/muscle-mass-foods-05.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Antioxidants are good for your body and fruits are filled with them!]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/22/muscle-mass-foods-06.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[More specifically – egg whites. You don’t need the yolk for your protein intake, and the yolk is the part that holds all the ridiculously high cholesterol, but you can add it if you want.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/22/muscle-mass-foods-07.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Fiber is good for you! Oatmeal will also decrease your hunger significantly, which means you’ll put a lot less unhealthy stuff in your mouth.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/22/muscle-mass-foods-08.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[These bad boys are almost pure protein, so this is an easy way to add up on those protein without adding too much calories to your diet.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/22/muscle-mass-foods-09.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[While these have a high calorie count, they also have a decent amount of protein and phosphorus – which helps burn fat during exercise.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/9-cutest-animals-with-gigantic-ears/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-28T08:29:09+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/17/cutest-animals-with-gigantic-ears-5.jpeg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[9 Cutest Animals With Gigantic Ears]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/17/cutest-animals-with-gigantic-ears-1.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Naturally, a beast that can’t see too well (which by the way, is a myth but I needed a segue) must have one or more of its senses heightened. California leaf-nose bat’s hearing would put to shame even the most advanced human technology! Out of all the bat species in the world, these guys have the biggest ears, which they use to hunt bugs in the dark. You know, echolocation.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/17/cutest-animals-with-gigantic-ears-2.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[You’ve all seen rabbits either in the wild or on TV, so you know their most distinctive feature is a pair of long ears. But not all rabbits are created equally. The black-tailed jackrabbit, which you can find in the western United States and Mexico. These big ears are useful for locating the potential danger.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/17/cutest-animals-with-gigantic-ears-3.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Who’s a cute kitty? This African serval is the cutest feline I’ve ever seen! And look at those humongous ears… d’awww! 10/10 would get scratched to death just to cuddle this beast.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/17/cutest-animals-with-gigantic-ears-4.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Pretty obvious that the African Bush elephant is on this list. Big flat ears, weighs a ton, got a handy-dandy trunk. It’s an elephant, people, what did you expect? But did you know that elephants flap them back and forth, creating air currents, to get some chill? Neat!]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/17/cutest-animals-with-gigantic-ears-5.jpeg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[This little ugly fellow is called the aye-aye, and it’s a lemur (technically). Aye-ayes are famous for their extra-long middle finger, and freaky eyes. However the ears aren’t small either, and it’s all that matters for this list. Next!]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/17/cutest-animals-with-gigantic-ears-6.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Can you believe people call these adorable squirrel-looking primates Bush Babies? Big eyes and ears, fluffy fur… they’re basically like cats! Only their cry in the middle of the night sounds like a human baby is being eaten alive. That and the eyes shining in the night was enough for the African kids to mistake the Galago for demons.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/17/cutest-animals-with-gigantic-ears-7.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[These little rodents from Mongolia and Western China have extremely oversized ears, hence their name – long-eared jerboa. Usually their ears are 30% longer than their heads, which is quite a feat.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/17/cutest-animals-with-gigantic-ears-8.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Judging by their name, Rabbit Bandicoots aka Bilby are from Australia. And hey, look at that, they are. Possibly one of the few creatures on that won’t kill you in the good old ‘Straya. The sad part is that these fluff balls are currently one of the endangered species, but people are trying to correct this grave injustice.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/17/cutest-animals-with-gigantic-ears-9.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Saved the best for last! Fennec fox is without a doubt the most lovable, huggable critter on this planet! And its large ears are the most adorable out of all the competitors. I can’t believe fennecs can hear their prey moving even underground! Their beauty became their biggest weakness. People are selling them as pets on the black market, and as much as I’d love to have one, poaching these lovelies should be punishable by death. Not the most popular opinion, but what can you do.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/9-facts-about-winter-weather/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-28T08:30:03+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/13/winter-weather-facts-07.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[9 Facts About Winter Weather]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/13/winter-weather-facts-01.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[You might not expect this, but even the Atacama Desert in Chile once received almost 32 inches of snow. And this is one of the driest places on earth!]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/13/winter-weather-facts-02.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Don’t use a mild day as an excuse to go out without your winter wear. The biggest cold snap in history saw the temperature (in South Dakota in 1911) drop from 55°F to 8°F in only fifteen minutes.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/13/winter-weather-facts-031.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[This seems a bit weird since it’s the coldest time of the year, but our temperature has nothing to do with our relative distance to the sun. It’s the axis at which the Earth tilts that determines temperature – hence why both hemispheres have summer and winter at different times.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/13/winter-weather-facts-04.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[According to science, the perfect snow-to-water ratio is 5:1.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/13/winter-weather-facts-05.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[In fact, two identical snowflakes were documented as far back as 1988! It’s safe to assume there’s been other snowflake twins since then.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/13/winter-weather-facts-06.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Which is actually quite fast. And this is just for the broad, parachute-like snowflakes. Pellet-like snowflakes drop even faster.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/13/winter-weather-facts-07.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[Snow has loads of air in it, which means that pretty much every inch of water can produce about ten inches of snow. That’s a pretty amazing difference, isn’t it?]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/13/winter-weather-facts-08.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[If you calculate this per person, that’s about 137 pounds of salt for every citizen in the United States.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/13/winter-weather-facts-09.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[This Japanese city gets plummeted with about 312 inches of snow every year.]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
<url>
<loc>https://nexolist.com/elon-musk-its-a-totally-rocket-science/</loc>
<lastmod>2019-08-26T08:13:03+03:00</lastmod>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/4/42.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/4/gallery/44-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/4/gallery/42-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/4/gallery/43-1024x585-thumbnail.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/4/43-1024x585.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/4/42.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
<image:image>
<image:loc>https://nexolist.com/media/posts/4/44.jpg</image:loc>
<image:title><![CDATA[]]></image:title>
</image:image>
</url>
</urlset>